<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SLU DSS openGIS Project</title>
    <link>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SLU DSS openGIS Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://slu-openGIS.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>The openGIS project is a collaborative effort with SLU students to curate and host GIS data about the St. Louis area in an accessible manner. Additionally, work on software engineering projects to create and maintain tools for working with local data. As with the DSS, we are also dedicated to creating a welcoming, inclusive data science community here at SLU (see the ‘Inclusion and our Code of Conduct’ section below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annoucing tidystl</title>
      <link>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/news/tidystl_annoucement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/news/tidystl_annoucement/</guid>
      <description>Today we&amp;rsquo;re excited to share the preview of the tidystl ecosystem - a family of R packages for wrangling spatial data with a particular emphasis on the City of St. Louis.
 areal - areal weighted interpolation (released onCRAN; website and GitHub repo) censusxy - batch geocoding using the Census Bureau&amp;rsquo;s API (beta release; GitHub) compstatr - tools for working with St. Louis Metropolitan Police Department crime data (under review for CRAN; website, and GitHub) gateway - access spatial data about St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Launch</title>
      <link>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/news/sitelaunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/news/sitelaunch/</guid>
      <description>We now have a website!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://slu-openGIS.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>The SLU Data Science Seminar is the host of Chris Prener&amp;rsquo;s openGIS project. The project is a collaborative effort with SLU students to curate and host GIS data about the St. Louis area in an accessible manner. We also maintain several R packages that contain tools for working with spatial data. More details about our projects and our commitment to creating an inclusive, welcoming data science community are available on our About page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>